现在  在Android Studio里  你可以点击运行按钮
Now in Android studio, you can hit the play button
在手机上运行应用
to run the app on your device.
在设备选择对话框中  可看到与电脑相连的移动设备
In the device Chooser dialog, you should see your connected device.
要想在之后的运行时不弹出该对话框  选中这个复选框即可
To prevent the dialog from popping up in future times, check this box,
点击OK按钮  稍等片刻
and then hit OK to continue. Within a few moments,
就可以看到Sunshine已经在手机上跑起来了
you should see it on your phone.
另外  Raido也提到过
On the other hand, as Raido was mentioning,
你还可以使用命令行工具
you can use command line tools.
在项目的根目录下  用gradlew命令在Mac或者Linux平台上
From the root folder of the project, use grade lw to build your app
来构建你的应用
on Mac or Linux.
如果你使用Windows系统  请查看视频下方笔记中的链接
Check the link in the notes below if you're using Windows.
第一行命令使gradle wrapper脚本命令获取到权限
This first command grants execution permission
这条命令只需要执行一次
to the gradlw rappers script. And you only need to do it the first time
以后在命令行中构建应用时就不需要再执行了
you're trying to build from the command line.
执行./gradlew assembleDebug命令可调试程序  在应用构建成功之后
Then you can call grade lw assemble debug. Once the build is successful,
在app/build/apk路径下会生成一个apk文件
it creates an APK file at the app/build/apk directory.
可使用adb命令进行安装apk
You can use adb to install the app. The -r command means
-r参数表明若应用已存在
that you can replace an existing version
则进行覆盖安装
of the app if you've already done it before.
有关adb命令使用的更多技巧  请看下方的教学笔记（Instructor Notes）
For more tips on adb, you can see the instructor notes below.
你可以使用adb shell am命令启动MainActivity
Then you can use this adb command with the activity manager tool
手机屏幕上也会立刻显示本次执行的结果
in order to start the main activity. And there you see it on the device.
我们看到应用已经能够在手机上运行起来了
And now we see it running in our phones.
Woo hoo  来碰个拳头~
Woo hoo! Fist bump!
目前进展一切顺利  让我们去找Dan来设计sunshine的UI界面吧  Woo~~
We're on a roll. Let's go find Dan so that we can build up the sunshine UI. Woo!